"Imperial Ballad"
here
Brother, look
Just dug it out
Damn you guys
What are you doing, you guys?
What are you doing?
Do you have humanity?
It's so unconscionable
Give me my mother back
Killed someone
This is simply out of control, really
His family's grave was also dug up
Uncle Lu
This is given to you as a filial piety
My mother's body
Please raise your hand and return it to me
Let her old man be laid to rest in peace
this is just ransom
ransom?
All the land on this mountain
It all belongs to our brothers.
all of you
You are not allowed to bury your family here
unless
Pay us a body insurance fee every year
This way I will make my brother
Find a good place to bury your mother
How about it?
-Mother-How is this possible?
This mountain has ancestors for generations
Those buried are all our relatives
When did it become your family?
-That's right.-That's right.
What are you doing? let me go y'all
Aren't you afraid of retribution?
God
let me go
retribution?
There will be no retribution for the dead
what to do?
What else can be done
Go back quickly
Go raise money
Walk…
-Raise money-Shopkeeper Jia
Doesn't he want his father's body back?
It's better now
I reunited them
The group...is reunited
Reunion...
What about you, what do you think?
Either you take your mother's corpse
Carry it home for me, or...
I buy…
I buy
Ask you to hand over the money
Do you have to ask my eldest brother to say it a second time?
come over
-Who asked you to come? -Big brother
The gang leader won't let me do anything these past two days.
I'm so bored
Don't you just charge mortuary fees?
I can do that too
Don’t you know why I won’t let you do it?
Don't you know how big a mistake you made?
If it weren't for the gang leader's court,
Our Huxiao Gang has been exposed
Big brother
Can't I just follow you?
Get out of here quickly
-Brother-go away
Keep digging for me
-well
Ten years of cold window
Today I finally become a minister
Standing in front of the emperor's steps
Mr. Meng’s official robe is really dazzling
But I will enter the palace later
Don't be frightened by this battle and your legs will weaken.
When Mr. Xiao Shen went to court for the first time
Could it be that he was so scared that his legs went weak?
How is it possible?
Then Mr. Shen, you might as well tell me
What does the Holy Father look like when he is in court?
I wonder if Mr. Meng has heard of this sentence?
Calling you a companion is like accompanying a tiger
I've heard of it
Our Holy Lord is angry
That's thunder and wrath
Last month a colleague
Because I said some nonsense during the performance
Directly dismissed from office and investigated
There is another colleague
Because it offended Long Yan
Directly…
But don't worry
For Zhili's sake
I will never stand idly by
Who dares to make things difficult for you then?
I, Shen Zhishu, will let him...
Mr. Meng, I haven’t finished speaking yet.
The Holy One has arrived
Welcome Your Majesty
Hail, holy bow
All the ministers are equal
thank you
elder sister
The autumn wind brings coldness, be careful to catch a cold
What happened to make our family’s talented girl Shen
Are you so worried?
Want me to say
Nothing happens
It's something that a drink can't solve.
It seems like something is really bothering you.
The Holy One has decreed
Transfer me to the post of associate director of the Procuratorate of Justice
Go help Mr. Meng
Punishing rape and eradicating evil in Kyoto
The Holy One wants to reuse you.
But his arrangement this time was unexpected.
Even I haven't had any air
The Chawen Yuan is responsible for correcting and impeaching corruption.
The flash of swords and shadows are inevitable
I'm afraid of blood
And prefer tranquility and elegance
It is clearly more suitable to stay in the Hanlin Academy
Silly sister
The Holy One wants to use you
It must have a deep meaning
This is where we rely on to punish rape and eradicate evil.
rather than brute force
You have been smart since childhood
Things that others can't do
for you
It's all a piece of cake
You said it quite easily
The Procuratorate was first established
Let’s not talk about those ruffians and how difficult they are to deal with.
These smiling tigers in the hall
I don’t know how many stumbling blocks have been prepared behind the scenes.
And this time even you
I can't even guess the Holy Spirit's intention
How could I not worry?
elder brother
Sister Zhili’s concerns
Not unreasonable
This Hanlin Academy is noble and stable
Best suited to my sister’s temperament
but
His Majesty's transfer came suddenly
Not as good as
We will meet the saint tomorrow to express our love.
Ah Nian still understands me
This move is holy.
Although it’s hard to guess
But from what I know about him
He must have thought carefully about it
After all, who are you cheating on?
-You can’t cheat our family’s etiquette-Brother
But I think
-Your Majesty, he did this... -A Nian
Then tell me
Your Majesty always treats us like brothers
The most reliance and trust in us
Now is the time to employ people
In addition to knowing etiquette
Who else can do it?
The position of associate director of the Inspectorate of Justice?
So since the Holy One has arranged it this way
I'll just go
That's right
You join forces with Lord Meng
It will definitely scare those silverfish.
how?
Am I some kind of scourge?
You have to sit so far away from me to take a bath
In the past, when I was reading with you in the East Palace
The Holy One is just a little more transparent and thoughtful than others.
But now the Holy One is in control of the Right Prime Minister’s Kingdom
The sword is pointed at Zuo Xiangguo, moody
If we are wrong in our words and deeds
The four of us grew up together
There are still few mistakes in your words and deeds
Come
Are there any outrageous words today?
Let me open my eyes
Let’s make a deal first, the Holy One can’t be angry
At least within the hour of soaking in the hot springs
You when the Holy Emperor was still a prince
OK
How dare you?
Shen Zhishu
This is my first attempt to test the waters.
The Holy Sage Jinsou Yuyan said that he would not be angry.
I'm not angry
I just suddenly thought of it
When I was the prince
How did I teach you a lesson?
Your Majesty
Holy lord, have mercy on me
Ah Nian, why are you still standing there?
I haven't felt as relaxed as I did today for a long time
I am sixteen years old
Hunting on behalf of heaven
Traveled through seven prefectures and nineteen counties in Daning
Now he can't even leave the palace
Also look at the almanac
The Holy Master pretended to be drunk last time
Otherwise, Zuo Xiangguo would be so angry
Did you hand me a ticket to report your illness?
Why are you still worried?
How could he complain about illness?
Half of the officials handed the memorial to his bed
He clearly became an auxiliary minister in the government.
Isn't it because I made him lose face?
He wants to give me a showdown?
The memorial presented now
Either…
It is necessary to strictly review the performance evaluation of female officials
Or you can urge me to establish a queen in order to secure the foundation of the country.
This stubborn old man
Clearly carrying the airs of being a veteran of three dynasties
Waiting for the Holy Spirit to invite him in person
Now at the beginning of the establishment of the Procuratorate
I wish he could rest for a few more days
Save yourself the trouble
Yesterday, Youxiangguo used the excuse of appreciating paintings
Invite Mr. Meng and Sister Zhili to the banquet alone
This seems to be an attempt to win over
I heard sister Zhili say
This matter between the Right Prime Minister and the Chawenyuan
Extraordinary care
He also said that he would spare no effort to help
This right prime minister’s country is obvious
Fighting with Zuo Xiangguo
Lord Meng's new official takes office
I'm afraid I'll suffer a lot.
If she can't even bear this little pain
Then how can she still be in charge of the Procuratorate?
Mr. Meng, I don’t know.
Our family knows that etiquette must be too much to bear.
But then again
Zuo Xiangguo wants to urge the establishment of a queen
Not entirely wrong
Put aside your handsome face
That's your temper
Be bold and bold all day long
stand down
Which girl dares to get close?
What did you say?
Look, I was right
Zhili and Sheng are childhood sweethearts
When I was young, I used to call Brother Ying, Brother Ying
Look now
The way she looks at the teacher
-Much gentler than watching the Holy One.-You are talking nonsense.
Sister Zhili only respects You Xiangguo
The Right Prime Minister is nearly half a century old
He still has a family
I know how to carry a shelf all day long
-How could sister Zhili... -You kid?
Spend the whole day in the martial arts arena
Were you stupid after wrestling with the Divine Guards?
How do you know what girls are thinking?
Your Majesty, don't always keep a straight face.
Otherwise, no girl would dare to approach you.
Most of the time I
Do you still smile more?
You are hiding a knife behind your smile
Smiling is scarier than not smiling
Then tell me
In our palace
Who else
Do you dare to be the same as you?
Who?
drink yours
Come, drink
-Cheers-Cheers
Could it be possible that Your Majesty was right?
An hour has come
Are you sure you want to continue?
Master Meng
Give me
Thanks
Assistant Shen
Could it be that the study room at home has been emptied?
They're just used items.
I was thinking
Bring two maids to sweep
But I’m afraid that my brother and Anian will laugh at me
Saying that the official office is a boudoir
I almost forgot the most important thing
This pot of fragrance fills the courtyard
I planted it myself
To Mr. Meng
Put it on the desk
The most peaceful
The aroma is indeed pleasant
First day in office
Let's take this cold court
How about becoming the most elegant official office in Kyoto?
good
How unreasonable
The Chawenyuan belongs exclusively to the Holy One
Taking office today
Not even the house has been repaired
The Chawenyuan is outside the Liangxiang and Liubu departments.
Zuo Xiangguo has a big opinion on me again
Wen Tao, the Minister of Hubu, was his confidant
Naturally he refused to approve the money
Just give me a kick in the ass
Is it just about repairing the house?
I am most familiar with it
Go find a cool place to rest
Leave it to me here
Master Meng
Today is your first day in office.
How can you do your own work?
How about I go back to my house and find some servants to help me?
No problem, no need to bother
Who's on top?
Master Meng
we have met
You are the one...
I am Yin Qing
Palace medicine man
What are you doing in our Procuratorate?
No one here buys rouge and gouache
wait for me
I am in the palace for a living
Forced
Ever since that day you handed me over to Colonel Di
Then I fully realized
Now I have washed my hands in a golden basin
If adults need spices in the future,
I give it away for free, no money required
What is this going to do?
Exorcise evil spirits
Peach wood drives away evil spirits
Bronze mirror reflects evil spirits
It's a haunted house after all
Don't prepare anything
Can't sleep well at night
-Haunted house? -Haunted house?
Mr. Meng and Associate Shen don’t know something.
here
It was once the interrogation wing of the Prison Department of the Ministry of Punishment
hear
Anyone who has been interrogated here
They all committed suicide out of fear of sin
Later, because it was too evil
It was abandoned
This is simply too deceiving
How could such a place be granted to the Chawenyuan?
Master Meng
Yesterday at the banquet, the teacher also said
If someone deliberately makes things difficult
He will never sit idly by
Let's go find him now
etc.
Assistant Shen is not afraid
I've been prepared
Wait until I finish this ritual
No matter what kind of evil ghost he is
All retreated
She is bleeding
adult
-Zhili-This is the Ningshen Dew I developed
Restores the mind and refreshes the mind
etc.
Is your medicine really effective?
adult
You can doubt my character
But you can't question my craftsmanship
wake up wake up
your mouth
Know the etiquette
-Zhili-do it again
What does this smell like?
It stinks so much
This is my pick-me-up
adult
Everything went wrong for Assistant Shen when he first arrived.
It can be seen that this yard is too dark.
In this case, why don't you wear this of mine?
Cinnabar bracelets to ward off evil spirits
I don't need it, I'm lucky
I want
I want it no matter how much
Only ten taels
Of course
Five taels is also acceptable
For Lord Meng’s sake
Just give it to Associate Shen
Why is this so embarrassing?
Master Meng
do you think
I'm a bit squeamish
Unqualified for the position of Associate Director
Will it hold you back?
What nonsense did you say?
When you placed a military order at the gate of Xu Mansion
I can see that you are not an ordinary daughter of a harem
Tell the truth
I originally thought you would be dissatisfied with the bloody storm in the academy
Will decline the position of associate director
But today
You came to your appointment with all the elegance in the courtyard
I'm surprised and happy
It's you
Being courteous for nothing
Come to my court
What is the purpose?
adult
I heard that the Holy One established the Chawenyuan
Allow adults to personally select assistants
I am willing to be your lord, I am willing to be your holy majesty
make a contribution
What about these roof tiles?
Did you repair them all?
yes
in this palace
I'm always where I need to be
Often one is the best
If you two adults need it,
Even if you tell me
Although I only have the skills of a three-legged cat
But the Five Elements Bagua
Feng Shui
Rejuvenate and detoxify
Mechanism number
I'm proficient in everything
Are you really just a palace official?
I listen
Rather, he looks like a strange person in a storybook
Assistant Manager Shen promoted me
adult
This is my latest development
Not smelly, not smelly
Pearl whitening powder enhanced version
I see that you have become a little tanned recently.
I'm not interested in any of this
Then let me see
Come to the Procuratorate
What is the purpose?
adult
After the True and False Society Yuan Case
Return to the Restoration Woman Enko
I have great admiration for adults
Adults are courageous and talented
Have the ability, have...
Anyway, he is different from those pedantic people
Your Excellency and I are both from poor backgrounds.
If you can follow the adults
There must be a future
certainly
I came here to surrender.
If you don’t have some skills
Why do you have the nerve to come?
adult
This is my new poison, colorful and colorful
Colorless and odorless
Take one bite
It makes people lose their fighting ability
You want to poison me?
I'm so thirsty
Huang Yuwei
-Are you okay? -Are you okay?
Are you okay?
Something happened
Mr. Meng’s first day in office
Your Majesty asked me to come over and take a look
If you encounter trouble when handling the case
The scepter can be used at any time to command the Divine Guards
You can also go directly to the palace to report to the Holy Emperor.
Huang Yuwei
your voice…
How does my voice sound...
Is it my voice?
What happened to my voice?
Yin Qing, where is the antidote?
Huang Yuwei, eat this
Half the time to burn incense
You should be able to recover
heroic male voice
How can I report this to the Holy Father?
This sound…
Shouldn't it be like this for the rest of your life?
Can it be done thoroughly?
Where is this medicine?
It's my new research
There should be some side effects
Like this Huang Yuwei
You go back and take a nap today
You should be fine when you get up tomorrow
How dare you poison me
No...Master Meng
I originally wanted to recommend this medicine myself.
I want my own drink
Huang Yuwei drank the medicine when he came, and I...
Is there something wrong with your brain?
What normal person would poison himself?
I now suspect you of poisoning and plotting to kill the imperial guards.
You come with me now
No, Master Meng...
Huang Yuwei
Yin Qing is my first colleague in the Chawenyuan
This is all a misunderstanding
Please don't embarrass him
Huang Yuwei
I prove
This medicine is indeed what he wants to drink
Don't let me do anything wrong in the future
I'll say goodbye now
Hard
walk slowly
Mr. Meng, you agree with me to join the Procuratorate.
you just saved my life
You are my lucky star
nobleman
-I will listen to you no matter what you say from now on - Sir
Do you really want to keep him?
Although our Chawenyuan is small,
But never leave useless people behind
you
stay for now
To be investigated
Not too small, not too small, useful and useful
Inspection and inspection, I went to work
adult
What are you looking at?
nothing
Where did you find these people?
The wives and daughters of these craftsmen
They are all my regular customers
I promise
As long as they are willing to help
Come to me to buy rouge at half price from now on
You really can do anything
He's also good at doing business.
If Fu Zhi knew you
We must be able to chat
I have no plans to get married yet
What you think is quite beautiful
By the way, my lord
Don't talk about me yet
The backyard is tidied up and the food is ready
Let's eat first
Don't leave it there, move over there
Mr. Meng, Assistant Manager Shen
I personally made a few specialty side dishes
Try it quickly
- You sit down and eat together too - How is this so embarrassing?
please
Yin Qing
Your craftsmanship is really amazing
Assistant Shen
But the food is not to your liking?
No
I'm just interested in diet
Just a little picky
If you have any requests, just ask
I will definitely correct it
In fact, there are no requirements
Like this fried meat with lettuce
Lettuce needs to be cut into sections to be tasty
The meat should also be cut as thin as cicada wings.
And this snowy soup
Fungi need to be harvested during the Yin period
After noon, it smells like earth
And this stir-fried seasonal vegetable dish
Sprinkle salt lightly and add less oil
It’s best not to add a drop of soy sauce
To preserve the original flavor
I just said it casually
Don't take it seriously
Actually I'm not very hungry either
Just not hungry
Now we have officially taken office
It is bound to bring the Tiger Roar Gang
and uprooted the forces behind him
Master Meng
We can find Jingzhaofu
Dali Temple Negotiation
Retrieve relevant files
But now all departments
There are quite a few criticisms of the Inspectorate
If you follow this process
I'm afraid it will take ten days and a half.
If someone deliberately makes things difficult
You can ask the Holy One to make a decision
I can also ask the teacher to come forward to negotiate
But such a small thing
We also want to alarm the Holy Emperor and Right Prime Minister.
Wouldn’t it make people think that our Chawenyuan is a soft persimmon?
What is Nada Yu's plan?
Gangs do evil
It’s nothing more than amassing ill-gotten wealth
And making money under the prosperity
Often the most hidden
Changle Street
There may be some clues
After the opening of Bo Feng Building
It can be used as a place for us to gather information.
Yin Qing
arrive
Go get the gong
I want to do big things
OK
Procuratorate handles cases
The Holy Father established the Chawenyuan
Aiming to eradicate gangsters and eliminate evil
Anyone who knows any clues about the Huxiao Gang
Anyone can come to the Procuratorate to report
Who is the Tiger Roar Gang?
What have you committed?
Let the court
Come to investigate with great fanfare?
The imperial court sent a female official to investigate the case
It's probably not a serious case.
Let's break up...
- Let's break up, everyone - you...
Nothing to see, let's go
Gone…
adult
This method
It seems to be of no use.
It seems that the Tiger Roar Gang is hiding very deep.
It’s not as ostentatious as Black Tiger Hall, where everyone knows
But as far as I know
Go to Jingzhao Mansion and Dali Temple every day
Complain against local gangsters
There are not a few people who report their grievances
Inspectorate of Justice
Aiming to protect the people
Any crime of committing adultery
bully
Anyone can sue
I will definitely make the decision for you
adult
get it for me
I didn’t expect there to be such a dilapidated place in Beijing.
There are mostly poor people in the north of this city.
A place where refugees and beggars gather
Associate Shen was born
The noble girl in the high gate in the east of the city
Nature has never been here
adult
Things that can be sold at home
All have been sold
I collected another twenty taels from my mother's family.
But there are still more than ten taels left
Thanks for your hard work
You were seriously injured by those group of body thieves
Not recovered yet
Never stay here
grandmother
Unfilial grandson
They stole my grandfather's body
Let us redeem it at a high price
But we simply can’t get enough
Money to redeem my grandfather’s body
Now even if you are past the first seven
I don't even dare to let you be buried
I'm afraid of those ungrateful corpse thieves
I stole your body again
come to blackmail us
grandmother
We really have no way out
Who is outside?
Procuratorate handles cases
you
That female official on the street just now
Get out quickly, get out quickly
We don't mean any harm
I just saw you frowning on the street
Worry that you will encounter difficulties
Let's find out what's going on
The Chawenyuan is directly under the Holy Sage
Act on behalf of the emperor
You tell Mr. Meng
Just talk to the saint
adult…
Ah Cheng
Ah Cheng, I can’t say
Having said that, my grandfather’s body cannot be redeemed.
We also reported the case to the government
But the government thinks we are a small matter
ignore
Instead, we were attacked by those body thieves
intimidation, revenge
adult
We really have no way out
Corpse thief?
How about it?
How do I feel about my outfit today?
Chen calls himself the most popular person in Changle Street
I saw the Holy One with such makeup today
I can only take off this title.
If the ladies of Kyoto see the Holy Lord,
Wouldn’t it make your mouth water?
Okay, stop flattering me.
How should I get out of the palace today?
I recently looked through old files
Found an abandoned passage
Direct access to the outside of the palace
lead the way
cousin
During his tenure as Cai Feng Envoy
Work tirelessly and forget about food and sleep
Running around day and night
Finally found this
This Huiyinfang has the best rules
It is necessary to submit the name card half a month in advance to make an appointment.
Questions for each distinguished guest
Musicians improvise
Waiting for the end of the song
There will also be a cup of specially blended tea with a hint of music.
The owner of the shop, Situ Xue, has become famous in the past two years.
Known as the best dancer in Kyoto
How many people spend a lot of money
Just to see its beauty
cousin
During the Flower Festival a few days ago
Why don't you praise the unique begonia between her eyebrows and eyes?
Okay, where are the clues?
Cousin, it’s not easy to get out now
What's the rush?
here
Learn to enjoy first
please
It is indeed Xiyanhua
Master Shen
No see for a few days
The owner's appearance becomes more and more clear
Mr. Shen hasn't been to Huiyinfang for some time.
Many rich ladies
Waiting to meet Mr. Shen
All in vain
Who is this young man?
This is my distant cousin He Du
He has been depressed recently
Come to me specially to relieve your boredom
He heard that Miss Situ
The sound of the piano can relieve a thousand sorrows
I came here to ask for a soothing song
My cousin is cold-tempered
Boss, please bear with me.
Since he is Mr. Shen’s friend
Of course I don't dare to neglect
This is a quiet room, one person per room
Best to be pure
Cousin, please talk slowly
Aribokubozu
I have heard for a long time that there is a special cave in Huiyinfang
The master's piano skills are outstanding
At first glance today
Sure enough, it lives up to its reputation
Young master deserves a prize
Just now I saw the young master looking at the screen repeatedly
Seems interested in it?
This quiet room
Green and elegant as far as the eye can see
Only on this screen
The purple flowers are very bright
The owner of the shop breaks elegance with beauty
It's quite ingenious
I wonder if it has any profound meaning?
It does have profound meaning
I was in Beijian a few days ago
There is a folk music workshop
Stayed at our hotel via Kyoto
I saw that the flower on the forehead of the musician was very unique
I specifically asked for advice
This flower is called Xiyan
Bloom in the night and wither in the morning
Symbolizing the moment of youth in Beijian
Very popular
Although my quiet room is elegant
But a little boring
I like this Xiyanhua again
So he sent people to build this screen.
If the young master likes it
How about giving it to the young master?
The shop owner kindly accepts it
I just occasionally flip through a few miscellaneous books
It is recorded that this flower has an oath to devour
It has the connotation of revenge and hatred
Young Master, be careful what you say
Huiyinfang opens its doors to welcome guests
What matters is being kind to others
Harmony is the most precious thing
I have no enmity or enmity with the Beijian people
I don't think he would lie to me.
Boss, there is no need to panic
The meaning of flowers
It is what people want
Everyone has their own understanding.
Young Master
tea please
good tea